all right I just watched Russell Brand's
new video that he posted today and I
loved it I loved it was about Tracey Mae
and her speech and how we need to allow
our leaders to be fallible and bring
emotion and the actual human beings and
yeah we do but that's not necessarily
going to happen because we've designed a
system where we need our leaders to look
like that that's who gets voted in that
- it's not going to change overnight
what we can do is create a space for us
to be actual real fallible human beings
to bring our true selves to the
conversation and how that conversation
means something and so that is what we
are gonna create together is a system to
be able to have deep conversations it
isn't about the anger and the tribalism
although that will come in pieces and we
will deal with it as it does but to
create the space where you can be a
fallible human being where you can make
mistakes and still be seen as worthy
because we're all worthy and society in
general with what it's currently doing
is not going to be able to give that to
us the biggest piece is doing it for
ourselves both as individuals to truly
love yourself let yourself be evaluable
a fallible human being allow yourself to
make mistakes
we don't need life to be edited
constantly just why I'm just going live
I don't know how to edit the video allow
it to just happen and we can we are
going to I am we are creating the space
online to be able to have conversations
so that we can be seen and heard in
small groups not this giant expert at
the top the politicians lady in like we
can have the actual conversations that
lead to real world change by creating
the the technology that allows that to
happen and that is what we're going to
do by having those conversations having
real meaningful conversations and part
of those conversations a fraction of
conversations are about how do we make
this process better how do we make the
technology that makes us be able to
bring these conversations together in a
way that's usable
do we work with people that we maybe
don't get along with that we do see
different sides of things what can we
agree on what can we build together how
do we come together and create an actual
system based on logic so that we can
also have a system about going
internally and doing the internal work
when we're freed up to do that we've met
our needs and it's it's a continual
process some people are gonna be
figuring out how to feed us some people
may be figuring out how to how to give
us energy other people are gonna be
figuring out how to do the emotional
work as individuals and groups and
giving those tools to people we are
capable of so much
no single human being has to do it all
there are enough people who are amazing
because every person is amazing and I'm
II don't mean I mean in your normal
nacinda markable ness allowing that
piece allows your piece of remark
ability to come out or genius you're
what you were put here to do and
everybody has that and it can be mundane
to the outside it is not mundane when
you tap into it when it is you find what
you were here for it's not about ego and
power and prestige for not for me anyway
it is about like Oh even I get to do
this even if I've never known for it
even if I never make a penny on out of
it I get to start the conversation
that creates a way for every human being
to be seen and heard and and through
those conversations that we are going to
create together we are gonna save
humanity the power of a conversation
without having the sanctimonious that
everyone has to be perfectly exactly
where I am bring you as you are and we
are gonna continually fail in the right
direction of success we are gonna figure
out oh well that didn't work now we need
to make that work we didn't get along
that was conflict and you know what you
learn and grow from conflict so we're
gonna have conflict and for people who
aren't in a space that they can handle
it right now we can have the
conversation how to minimize conflict
for you but it doesn't mean outlined it
all together
and it doesn't mean running away from it
it is bringing fallible human beings
together and having the conversations or
we find the common ground and are able
to create for the real human being not
for perfection and so I want to keep
this under five minutes I just wanted to
come on and share and I love the new
Russell Brand it's not he's not new give
us him save a self before to it just he
wasn't showing that his piece isn't
solved and so much of the people that
I'm listening to and what they say and
choosing to listen to them I like tail
Swan Russell friends um can't think I'll
sneeze I there is a lot of amazing that
is happening on this planet I mean you
allow and there's people who you're not
going to know serving um let's have see
them because it's like right my friend
in this conversation and and my mom and
my like it's seeing people allowing them
to be themselves and allowing that
triggering you you're real authentic
self and it's just like it's a
conversation verbal and nonverbal and we
are gonna have the actual verbal one
online so that everybody can participate
and as it gets more complex and we can't
handle the people I'm still figure out
how we have that conversation it's
looking like it's gonna be Google
Hangouts but if somebody else has a
better option please put it in the
comments let's figure it out I'm gonna
have a conversation on all the different
social media platforms because I do you
pretty wants to focus on all of them so
okay let's allow it let's allow it to do
what it wants to do that's so much
easier than making it pick one we are
gonna create a world that works for
everyone by having the conversation that
everybody is invited to please like and
subscribe and get in contact if this is
this world that you want to help create
together let's have the conversations
let's create the tech to do that thanks